Finding Aid for the Grantland Rice Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Newspaper clippings of poems, articles, and columns by Grantland Rice
  - Index of all poems, articles, and columns by Grantland Rice
    - The Duffer's Spring Song (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - The Duffer's Thrilling News (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - The Durable Entry (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Dust of Our Dead (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - The Dyer-Cronin Chorus (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - The Dying Winter (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - E. Duggan Stopped 'em (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Early Tip (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Early Tip to Louis and Conn (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - East Has Always Crushed Napoleons (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Easy Money for the Lucky Yank (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Echo Answers (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Edward G. Barrow (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Edward V. Cicotte (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Elegy in a Country Ballyard (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Elegy in an Empty Stadium (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Eleven Years (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Either That or a D-- F-- (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - The Empty Stocking (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Emulating G.W. (Box 5, Folder 12, Box 6, Folder 4, 22)
    - The End of Depression (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - End of the Road (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - The End Sunners (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Entrance Workouts (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - An Epic of the Fair (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - An Episode (Box 6, Folder 7, Box 7, Folder 16)
    - The Epoch of Strange Tongues (Cantos 1-2), (Canto 3) (Box 4, Folder 8, 9)
    - Equality (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - An Essay on 'The Fan' (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - The Eternal Fountain (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Even More So (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - 'Even This Shall Pass Away' (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Every Little Bit Helps (Box 4, Folder 3, 9)
    - Every Little Bit of a Fellow (Box 5, Folder 12, 29)
    - Everybody Works the Batter (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - The Exception (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - The Ex-Champion Speaks (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - The Exile--and Christmas (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - The Exile Hears the Call (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - The Exile's Revery (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Existence (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - The Expert's Dilemma (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Explaining (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Explaining the Dope (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Explaining Upsets (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - An Explanation (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Face to the Morning (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Facing Morning (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Facing the Storm (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Fair Warning (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Fame in the Field (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Fame Triumphant (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Fame's Epitaph (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Familiar Tunes (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Famous Dope Revisions (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Famous Sayings Up-to-Dated (Box 4, Folder 19, 20)
    - The Fan and His Way (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - The Fan Awakes (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - A Fan Episode (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - The Fan Revival (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - The Fanatic Exclaims (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - The Fanatic Reports (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - The Fanatical Angle (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Fandom's Viewpoint (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - A Fan's Confession (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - A Fan's Diary (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - The Fan's Recessional (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - The Fan's Rejoinder (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - A Fan's Reverie in a Country Ballyard (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - The Fan's Revery (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - The Fan's Spring Address (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - The Fan's Spring Song (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - The Fan's Viewpoint (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Far Away and Long Ago (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Farewell, Mr. Brummell (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Fate (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - The Fate of the Hardy (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Father grabs the paper" (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Father Willard (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Favorite Refrains (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Fear (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Feeling Like a Yankee (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - The Females (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - The Festive Game of Golf (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - A Few August Fancies (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - A Few Christmas Cards (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - A Few Lines to Kaiserbill (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - A Few Lines to Little Bill Johnston (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - A Few Lines to the Dodgers (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - A Few Lines to Tom Yawkey (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - A Few More Heroes (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - A Few New Year Resolutions (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - A Few Personal Thanks (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - A Few Rambling Thoughts (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - A Few Revisions (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - A Few Sport Revisions (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - A Few Thanksgiving Odes (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - A Few Up-to-Date Revisions (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - A Few Words of Advice (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - A Few Words to the Wise and the Dumb (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - The Fickle Lure (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Fierce (Two Ways) (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Fifty-Fifty (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - The Fight (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - The Fighter (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - The Fighter Speaks (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - The Fighter's Defiance (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - The Final Answer (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - The Finish (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Finn's Team Scalped (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - The First Game (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - First of All, Tell Me (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - The First Spring War Cry (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Fleeting Fancies (Box 4, Folder 4, 7)
    - Foolish Illusion (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Football Alphabet (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Football and Life (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Football Days (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Football Slegy for 1939 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - The Football Player's Rubaiyat (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Football Sketches (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - A Football Story (Box 3, Folder 29, Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Football's All-Americas (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Football's 1945 Formations (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Football's Omelet Title (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Football's Sad Lexicon (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - For General Use (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - For Old Times' Sake (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - For Pity's Ache (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - For the Glory of TCU (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - For the New Year (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - The Forbidden Language (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Ford Christopher Frick (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Fore! To Warren G. Harding (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Forgetting You (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - The Forgotten (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - The Foundation (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - The Four Horsemen (Box 8, Folder 16, 18)
    - The Fourth and the Flag (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - A Fragment (Box 4, Folder 27, Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Frank Condon (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Frank Leroy Chance (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Frank Menke's 'Encyclopedia of Sport' (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - "Friend of the years" (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - "Friend, should I meet you" (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - "Fringed by clouds the sun" (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - From a Duffer's Lexicon (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - From Barrack and Camp (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - From Dawn to Night (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - From Outside (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - From Oyster Bay to Beverly (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - From the Field (Box 5, Folder 14, Box 7, Folder 42)
    - From the Game (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - From the Island up the River (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - From the Off-Trail (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - From the Port of Play (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - From the Road (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - From the Sonnets of a Newsboy (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - From the Soul of the Crowd (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - From Two Viewpoints (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - The Front Line Speaks (Box 7, Folder 15, Box 5, Folder 20)
    - The Fugiting of Tempus (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Full Many a Putt (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - The Funeral March of Gotham (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - 'Fuzzy-Wuzzy' Marquard (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - The Game 4-29; 5-11, 15, 29 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - The Game and the Piper (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Game's End (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - The Game's Greatest Pitcher (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Gangway ! (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Gassed (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - The Gathering (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - The Genius (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - George W. Up-to-Dated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - A Georgia Ballade of Jan. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - The Georgia Rubaiyat (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - "Get out your leather" (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Gettin' Ready (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - The Ghost of a Dream (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - The Ghosts of Arcady (Box 4, Folder 24, Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Ghosts of the Alamo (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Ghosts of the Field (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - The Ghosts of Yesteryear (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - The Giants of Yesterday (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - The Gift of the Gods (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Gifts from the Gods (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Girl and the Game (Box 4, Folder 25, Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Given Your Choice (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Giving Due Credit (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Glenna Collett at Troon (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - The Glory of the Game (Box 5, Folder 13, Box 6, Folder 28)
    - The Goal (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - The Goat (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - God's Country (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - The Golden Years (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Golf and Life (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - A Golf Equation (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Golf in Europe (Box 5, Folder 13, Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Golf Instruction (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Golf Lessons (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Golf Mysteries (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Golf Stories (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - The Golf Veteran Speaks (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - The Golf Widow Reports (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - The Golfer Interjects (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - The Golfer's Alphabet (Box 5, Folder 15, Box 6, Folder 48)
    - The Golfer's Christmas Wish (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - The Gods of Yesterday (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - The Golfer's Dirge (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - The Golfer's Invictus (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - The Golfer's Mother Goose (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - The Golfer's Mr. Coue (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - The Golfer's Prayer (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - The Golfer's Return from the Front (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - A Golfing Medley (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - A Golfing Prophecy (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Golf's Main Stymie (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Golf's Mother Goose (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Gone Before (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Good Luck (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - The Good Old Days (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - The Good Ship Uncle Sam (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Goodby, Dolly Gray (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Goodby, Euclid (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - The Goods (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - The Grand Old Hag (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - The Grand Old Winter League (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - The Gray Reunion (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - The Gray Road (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - The Great Adventure (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - The Great Exception (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - The Great God 'Justice' (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - The Great WHEN (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - The Gridiron Alphabet (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Gridiron Glory (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Grif's Sad Wail of Lamentation (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Gypsy Gall (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Gypsy Heart (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Hail and Farewell (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Hail! Hail! the Gang's All Here (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Hail to the Peanut (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Hailing June (Box 5, Folder 8, Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Halloween at Uncle Mose's (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Hard Lines (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - A Hard Luck Yarn (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - The Hardest Query (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Harry Hawker (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - The Has-Been (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - The Has-Been Speaks (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Having a Corking Time (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - "He could make a bomb" (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - He Never Heard of Casey (Box 5, Folder 24, Box 7, Folder 17)
    - "He sang a song" (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - He Took His Vacation in New York (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - He Walked Right Out (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - The Head Coach (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Heading the List (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Heads Up! (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Heathen Chinee Is Outclassed (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Heavyweight Champions and Ex-Champions (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - The Height of Something (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Helen Wills (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Her Complaint (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Her Last Reunion (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Her Prayer (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Here's Looking at You, Dutchman (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Here She Comes (Box 5, Folder 12, 15)
    - Here They Are Again (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Here They Come Again (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Hiawatha Answered (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Hiawatha Gets the Fever (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Hickman's Ode to Melancholy (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - The Hidden Path (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - The Hidden Road (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The Hills of Fame (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Hilt to Hilt (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - His Complaint (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - His Umps, Joseph O'Brien (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - His Viewpoint (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - History in Review (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Home (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Home and Tennessee (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - The Home of Dream (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - The Home Sector (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - The Home Way (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Hoo's Hoo in Politics (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - The Hoodoo (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Hoodoo's Reply (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Hope Springs Eternal (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - The Horse or the Monk? (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - The Horse Player at Home (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - The Horse Player's Wail (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Hough Guest (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - How, Indeed? (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - How 'Mike the Bite' Won Glory (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - How Pugdom Views a Wise Old Saw (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - How the Poets Dope the Race (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - How to Keep Cool (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - How to Putt (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - How to Tell (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - The Human Race--and Evolution (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - An Humble Wish (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - The Hunch Incarnate (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - "A hundred dreams" (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - A Hundred Years from Now (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Hurdling a Barrier (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Hymn of Hate (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - I'm Afraid to Go Home from the Park (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - I Can Dream--Can't I? ' (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - I Can Still Dream (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - I Can't Do This Sum (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - "I do not know what I shall find" (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - I Don't Know Where I'm Going, But I'm on My Way (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - "I have followed endless dreams" (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - "I've seen a bale of umpires" (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - I Lift My Glass (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - I Remember--I Remember (Box 4, Folder 4, 25)
    - I Wonder (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - If Grantland Has His Say, Female Fans Will Have to Pay (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - If I Were Only King (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - If Jeffries Should Come Out Again (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - If That Call Bell Hadn't Rung (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - If They Were All Like Washington (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - If winter Comes (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - If You Don't Watch Out (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Immune (Box 6, Folder 2, Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Imparting Advice (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - An Impending Drama (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - In a July Orchard (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - In an Old Book Shop (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - In an Old Attic (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - In Any Game (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - In Appeal (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - In Answer (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - In Behalf of the Ball Player (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - In Boston Today (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - In Conclusion (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - In Defiance (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - In Memoriam (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - In Memoriam (R.H. Davis) (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - In Memoriam--The Naps (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - In Life--In Death (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - In Nashville (Box 4, Folder 18, 25)
    - In Passing (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - In Quick Rebuttal (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - In Rebuttal (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - In Reply (Box 3, Folder 7, 12, Box 6, Folder 47, 50)
    - In Retrospect (Box 4, Folder 15, 17)
    - In Revery (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - In the Bleachers (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - In the Chilly Night (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - In the Darkness (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - In the Dim Night (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - In the Dim Tavern (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - In the Land of Lost Dreams (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - In the Same Boat with Mr. Kipling (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - In the Shadows (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - In the South--Not Yet--But (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - In the Spring (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - In the Wake of Ben King (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - In the Wake of Mr. Coleridge (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - In Training (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - In Warning (Box 5, Folder 3, Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Incident of the Season (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Independence Day (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Insanity Flashes (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Into the Battle (Box 5, Folder 3, Box 7, Folder 39)
    - The 'Invictus' of Today (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Isn't Murphy the Hopeful One? (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - It Doesnit Take Much (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - It Has Happened So (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - "It isn't the speed" (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - It's This Way (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - It's Time Again (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - It's Up to the Naps to Deliver Now (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - "It's what should be" (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - J. Caesar Dropped a Game (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Jack Britton's Last Fight (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Jack Dempsey (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Jack Dempsey's Dream (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Jack Dillon and Preparedness (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Jack Quinn, Forty-two (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Jackson's Hit (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - James Gordon (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Jerome Dunstan Travers (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Jimmy Johnston (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Job for Undertaker (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Jobs for Teddy (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - John Henry Wagner (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Johnson in the Box (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - The Journey (Box 4, Folder 15, 20)
    - The Joy Killer's Dream (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Just a Hint (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Just a Peep into the Dream Book (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - "Just a tired little boy" (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Just a Wish (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Just for a Gamble (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Just Here and There (Box 4, Folder 17, 18)
    - Just the Same (Box 5, Folder 5, 22)
    - Just the Same in Days of Old (Box 4, Folder 9, 17)
    - Just to See La-Joy (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Just Twenty-Six Years Later (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Just What Is Morale? (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - June (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Jungle Echoes (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - 'Kid' Griffith and 'Young Jim' McGuire (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Kidnapper (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - King Cole and His Bowls (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - King Corn (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - The Kink in the Menu (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Kipling Number (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - A Knife in the Heart (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - The Knockers (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Knocking Advice (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Knocking Slang (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Knowledge (Box 4, Folder 23, Folder 5)
    - The Lament of Mr. Jeffries (Box 5, Folder 16, Box 4, Folder 2)
    - The Lamp of Aladdin (Box 4, Folder 18, 22)
    - The Land of the Bean and the Cod (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - The Land of the Last 'Twilight (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Land of the Long Time Ago (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - The Land Where the Children Dwell (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - The Land Where the Dead Men Dwell (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The Lane (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Larry the Literateur (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - The Last and Ultimate Straw (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - The Last Fight (Box 5, Folder 12, Box 6, Folder 18)
    - The Last Hope Gone (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - The Last Inn (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Last Lines to a Dying Year (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - The Last of All 6-24 (Box 7, Folder 21, Box 8)
    - The Last of the Troops (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - The Last Fort (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - The Last Ride (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - The Last Ride Together (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - The Last Road (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - The Last Stand (Box 5, Folder 12, Box 6, Folder 18)
    - The Last Tavern (Box 5, Folder 2, 29)
    - The Last to Leave (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - The Last Trail (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Last Trip South (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - The Last Twilight (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - The Latest Edict (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - The Latest Lyrical Lo11apalusa (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Latest Styles in Bores (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - The Latter Day Creed (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - The Laugh on Nero (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - The Law of the Game (Box 4, Folder 24, Box 6, Folder 56)
    - The Law of the Race (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Leading to a New One (Box 5, Folder 13, Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Learning Life's Lesson (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Leaving an Address (Box 5, Folder 15, Box 8, Folder 4, 21)
    - The Legions of Lee (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - The Legislative Situation (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - The Length of Time (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Let It Go at That (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Let's Dream Again--And Then-- (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Let Us Forget (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - "Let's look back" (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - "Let's play it out" (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - A Letter Home (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Life's Day (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Life's Philosophy (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Life's Treasures (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Light and Shadow (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - The Lights of Home (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Like the Yarn of the Nancy Bell (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Limericks of Swat (Box 6, Folder 54, 62)
    - Limericks of the Links (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - The Line Is Drawn (Box 4, Folder 2, Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Lines (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Lines from Sporting Poets (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Lines on the Hog (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Lines upon Looking a Gift Golf Club in the Face (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Lines to a Brace of Colonels (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Lines to a Cincinnati Fan (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Lines to a Few Old Sporting Friends (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Lines to a Freshman (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Lines to a Gas Company (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Lines to a Ghost (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Lines to a Halfback (Box 5, Folder 14, Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Lines to a Pitcher (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Lines to a Tragedy (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Lines to an Umpire (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Lines to Amos Rusie (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Lines to Any Golfer (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Lines to Certain Golfing Mates (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Lines to Ed Walsh (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Lines to F. Schulte (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Lines to Hughey Jennings (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Lines to J.D. Travers (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Lines to J. Dempsey (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Lines to J. 'Willard (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Lines to Lost Friends (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Lines to Miss Pankhurst (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Lines to Miss Ravenscroft (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Lines to Mrs. Pankhurst (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Lines to 1944 8-1 Lines to 1946 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Lines to Stuffy Mclnnis (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Lines to the Editor (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Lines to the 'weather Bureau (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Lines to 'Wrestlers (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Listed! (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Listen-- (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Literary Remorse (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - The Little Boy and His Dream (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Little Boy Blue Grows Up (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Little Dreamers (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - The Little Green Isle (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Little Hugh Bedient (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - The Little Land of Play (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Little Sweetheart (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The Little Tin Horn 4-27 (Box 5, Folder 11, Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Little Toddle-Legs (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - A Little Wasted Advice (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - "Lives of duffers" (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Lives There a Fan? (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Locating Spring (Box 7, Folder 45)